Van Fleet, David Collection of Academy of Management Records 6278
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
David Van Fleet Collection of Academy of Management Records
1931- 2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Van Fleet, David
6278
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records.
This collection consists of Academy Management correspondence, meeting minutes, Constitution, publications, annual reports and financial reports. Also included is volume I & II of Lectures On Types of Economic Theory, Delivered by Professor Wesley C. Mitchell at Columbia University. Alfred P. Sloan, Jr,'s book My Years With General Motors.
6416924
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
J. Woodward, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5289: AoM Records 5289 MB: AoM Memorabilia 5289 P: AoM Photographs 5289 PUBS: AoM Publications 5593: AoM Records 5593 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Material 5893m: Leonard R. Burgess "Status of Women in Academy of Management" Memoir 5904m: Paul Gordon Collection of Academy of Management Miscellany 5920 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Collection 5977 mf: AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm 6019: AoM Eastern Academy of Management Records 6117: AoM Additional Records 6134: AoM Publications Additional Publications
Mitchell, Wesley C. (Wesley Clair), 1874-1948; Sloan, Alfred P. (Alfred Pritchard), 1875-1966; Van Fleet, David; Academy of Management; Academy of Management. Southwest Division; Academy of Management. Fellows Group; Academy of Management. Board of Governors; Allied Southern Business Association; Southern Management Association
6416924
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, Reports (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Academy of Management Newsletter, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code of Ethics (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Southwest Division [folder 1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Southwest Division [folder 2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Southwest Division [folder 3 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Southwest Federation of Administrative Disciplines (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Southern Management Association [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Southern Management Association [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Southern Management Association, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Southern Management Association, Board of Governors (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Southern Management Association, Newsletter, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Southern Management Association, Newsletter, 2001-2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Southern Management Association, Misc. Documents [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Southern Management Association, Misc. Documents [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Southern Management Association, Starbuck (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Board, August 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board, Spring 1985 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Board, Spring 1985 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Board, December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Board, Pub. Rel./Exhibits Coor. Search Committee (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Board, Newsletter Editor Search Committee (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Regions, Regions 50th (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Regions, Regional - Centennial Project (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Regions, Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Board of Governors, August 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Board of Governors, Spring 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Board of Governors, December 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Board of Governors, August 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Policies and Procedures Manual (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Interest Groups (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Awards (Box 2, Folder 23)
- N-File and Working Papers, Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 24)
- N-File and Working Papers, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 25)
- N-File and Working Papers, Working Papers (Box 2, Folder 26)
- N-File and Working Papers, The N-File Newsletter, No. 1-10, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- N-File and Working Papers, The N-File Newsletter, No. 11-20, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- N-File and Working Papers, The N-File Newsletter, No. 21-28, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- N-File and Working Papers, The N-File Newsletter, No. 29-37, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Management History Division, Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Management History Division, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Allied Southern Business Association (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Academy of Management Fellows [folder 1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Academy of Management Fellows [folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Academy Task Force (Box 3, Folder 10)
- My Years with General Motors - Alfred P. Sloan (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Types of Economic Theory, Lectures by Wesley C. Mitchell, Volume I, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Types of Economic Theory, Lectures by Wesley C. Mitchell, Volume II, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 13)